Agustin Panizza

Full stack developer with a passion for programming. I started 10 years ago creating gameservers with C++ and Lua. Experience working in NodeJS, React, Redux, SQL among otherindustry technologies. I worked on the creation of an educational page for children that aimed to teach the main technologies to develop a website. With creative thinking, innovation, communication, proactivity and logical thinking

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Postgres, Sequelize, Scrum, MongoDb, MariaDb

WORK EXPERIENCES

Free lance – Staff Leader / Organization of the management team to achieve the best possible experience for users on video game servers with more than 300 simultaneous users 2013–2021.

Free lance - Development of video game servers using C++, Lua , MariaDb. 2013-2021.

PROYECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - Portfolio Visit

• Desing and develop the app using React, Redux, javascript, HTML and CSS.

Full Stack Web Developer - Pokemon App Visit may 22 - may. 22 Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop a Poke App that includes: searches, filtering, ordering and creation
- Develop the app using Front React, Redux, Pure CSS and Back developed in Node.js
 with Express. PostgreSQL and Sequelize database

Front End Web Developer - CodeLearn Visit jun. 22 - jun 22 Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Develop an educational app in group with 6 other developers that included :Authentication, ranking, user profile, course rating, payment gateway
- In this APP realize the design, responsive, all the CSS, course page, home,navigation bars & integrae redux/toolkit.
- Develop the app using Vite, Html, Javascript, React, Redux Toolkit and pureCSS, Google API was used ford authentication, Stripe was used in the payment gateaway, back end routes created with Express and Mongo Db for database.

Full Stack Web Developer - HP Grupos Electrógenos Visit Dic 22 - Dic 22

- This is a website I designed and developed for a generator company.
- It was developed using Html, Javascript, React, Redux Tool-kit, HTML and pure CSS for the Front End and Express with MongoDB in the Back End.

Personal details

Name

Agustin Marcos Panizza

Location

Berazategui / Buenos Aires

Phone number +5491154613888

Email

agustin_panizza@hotmail.com

Additional information

LinkedIn

Portfolio

www.agustinpanizza.com

Competencies

Eficient

Entrepeneur

Responsible

Honest

Results oriented

Languages

English

French Dfi

Spanish afi

BOOTCAMP

Full stack web developer

mar. 2022 - jul. 2022

Soy Henry

Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. +700hr of theoretical and practical course 2022.

(HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Postgres, Sequelize, Scrum).

EDUCATION

Sound engineer

abr. 2018 - oct. 2020

Tecson, Buenos Aires

Bachelor in systems

Universidad de La Plata, La plata / Buenos aires (2 full years)

System engineering

Utel nov. 2022 – jul. 2024

Intensive plan systems engineering (2 years, 8 months)